Guide to the Bellingham Municipal Dock records 1926-1972
Western Washington University, Center for Pacific Northwest Studies
Bellingham Municipal Dock records
1926-1972
Center for Pacific Northwest Studies Goltz-Murray Building 808 25th St Bellingham, WA 98225-9123 Phone: 360 650 7534 Email: cpnws@wwu.edu
XOE_CPNWS0090bellinghammunicipaldock
Port of Bellingham (Wash.)
3 linear feet
The collection consists of inbound/outbound tonnage logs, wharf manifests, a yearbook, and statistical data from the Bellingham Municipal Dock (later Citizens Dock).
The collection consists of inbound/outbound tonnage logs, wharf manifests, a yearbook, and statistical data from the Bellingham Municipal Dock (later Citizens Dock).
The collection is open to the public.
Acquisition information is unknown.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Port of Bellingham (Wash.)
Bellingham (Wash.)--History--Sources
Docks--Washington (State)--Bellingham--History--Sources; Harbors--Washington (State)--Bellingham--History--Sources; Transportation--Washington (State)--Whatcom County--History--Sources; Waterfronts--Washington (State)--Bellingham--History--Sources
Bellingham; Public Works
The following section contains a detailed listing of the materials in the collection.
- Inbound Tonnage Log (unbound), 1927-1932 (Volume 1)
- Inbound Tonnage Log, 1933-1947 (Volume 2)
- Outbound Tonnage Log (unbound), 1927-1932 (Volume 3)
- Outbound Tonnage Log, 1933-1947 (Volume 4)
- Wharf Manifest of Goods Delivered, 1926 March-1927 April (Volume 5)
- Wharf Manifest of Goods Delivered, 1953 (Volume 6)
- Port of Bellingham Yearbook, 1927 (Box 1)
- Marine Facilities of the Port of Bellingham, Undated (Box 1)
- Commitments Register, 1932 March 1-October 21 (Box 1)
- Statistical Data (scattered), 1951-1972 (Box 1)